<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Osberht the Umber</title><link>http://vsisk.io/osberht/</link><description>Recent content on Osberht the Umber</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://vsisk.io/osberht/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hartharrow</title><link>http://vsisk.io/osberht/posts/hartharrow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://vsisk.io/osberht/posts/hartharrow/</guid><description>Hartharrow is a coastal village of about 400 in northern Carse.
Primarily a fishing village, Hartharrow also has ample forested areas nearby that provides decent hunting and trapping for the populace. The soil around the village is not as rocky as that nearer to Rock Ridge, so it supports a varied selection of crops for farming. In fact, the town was renamed after a local&amp;rsquo;s invention of a harrow that utilized hart antlers to break up the still reasonably tough soil of the region.</description></item><item><title>Ingram</title><link>http://vsisk.io/osberht/posts/ingram/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://vsisk.io/osberht/posts/ingram/</guid><description>Ingram is the common (northern) raven familiar of the magi, Osberht the Umber.
He is about 2 feet long and weighs roughly 2.5 pounds.</description></item><item><title>Osberht the Umber</title><link>http://vsisk.io/osberht/posts/osberht-the-umber/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://vsisk.io/osberht/posts/osberht-the-umber/</guid><description>Osberht the Umber is a magi currently serving House Ardor of Carse.
Reserved, yet confident, young magi from Carse.
Early life He was born in Hartharrow.
Discovery He did something at the age of 8 to demonstrate his magical aptitude.
The White Tower Relationships Significant friend is missing or dead likely joined an adventuring group had a rival/enemy/nemesis from the Tower, who also hates Osberht by association gifted Osberht his maple-handled leatherworking tools Leatherworking instructor female instructor who helped him further his leatherworking skills the most majority of this wasn&amp;rsquo;t part of the regular curriculum Academic advisor male instructor who is the leading expert on portal magic Harrowing completed just before turning 20 dissertation on portal magic (port crystals and ferry stones) ideas: created a process for making ferry stones was an order of magnitude more cost efficient (the stones are formed as part of an alchemical process) improves stones to allow for return journey before being consumed Post-Harrowing continued research on portal magic discovered/created his dimension door spell finally had time to focus on crafting his adventuring equipment Petitioning House Ardor started at age 21 currently 23 or 24 room/cell in West Tower (overhanging canyon) Wigmund is the senior magi was able to visit his family during the journey to House Ardor from the White Tower Appearance Physical 6'0&amp;quot; 175 lb.</description></item></channel></rss>